Before you get started writing code,
在开始编写代码之前
here's a quick overview of the binomial class exercise.
先来大概了解一下 Binomial 类练习
The exercise is contained inside this 4a binomial package folder.
这个练习在 4a_binomial_package 文件夹中
Inside this folder, are quite a few files and a distributions directory.
其中有好几个文件以及 distributions 文件夹
Out of all these files,
在这些文件中
there are two that you're going to need to modify.
你需要修改其中的两个
First, is the init Python file inside the distributions directory here.
首先是 distributions 目录中的 init 文件
Currently, the init file only imports the Gaussian class.
现在 这个 init 文件只导入了 Gaussian 类
You'll first need to modify this file to also import the binomial class.
你需要修改该文件 使其也可以导入 Binomial 类
Going back, take a look at the binomial distribution file.
回到上一级看一下 Binomialdistribution 文件
You'll see that I've put in a bunch of to-do sections,
你会看到我在其中放了很多的 TODO 部分
to help guide you along.
帮助你完成代码
Make sure to read the to-dos,
一定要阅读 TODO 的说明
so that you understand what the code should look like.
这样你才能理解代码应该是什么样的
Each method also contains a docstring explaining the expected inputs and outputs.
每个方法还包含了一个描述预期输入输出的文档字符串
You'll see as well that I've included a file called test.py.
你还可以看到有个 test.py 文件
This file contains unit tests that
其中包含了单元测试
you can run to help you determine if your code is working properly.
你可以运行该文件帮助检测代码是否正确运行
Here's how to use this workspace.
接下来说一下如何在 workspace 使用该文件
First, you'll need to open a terminal and go into
首先 你需要打开一个终端
the package directory with the command cd 4a_binomial_package.
输入 cd 4a_binomial_package 进入软件包所在目录
Then you can type pip install.
然后你可以输入 pip install .
which will install the distributions package.
安装 distributions 软件包
The unit tests are in the tests.py file.
单元测试在 test.py 文件中
You can run the unit tests by typing Python test.py.
你可以输入 python test.py 运行单元测试
As you modify your code,
当你修改代码的时候
you can run the test.py file to see if your code is working.
你可以运行 test.py 文件确认代码是否正常
In this case, it tells me that from distributions,
在这次示例中 测试代码告诉我
import binomial in the test file doesn't work.
from distributions import Binomial 没有运行成功
That's because I never put it in the init file inside the package.
这是因为我还没有将代码写入 init 文件中
As you modify your code,
当你修改代码的时候
you can run the test.py file to see if your code is working.
都可以运行 test.py 文件来检测代码是否正确
However, whenever you update the package code,
不过每次更新软件包的代码
you need to reinstall the package.
都需要重新安装软件包
Otherwise, Python won't be able to see the changes you've made.
否则 Python 不能识别你做出的修改
You can reinstall the package by going to the terminal.
你可以重新安装软件包 进入终端
Again, making sure you're in the package directory and typing
再次确保你已经处于软件包所在目录
pip install dash dash upgrade, dot.
输入 pip install --upgrade .
You'll see that it uninstalls the package and then reinstalls it. That's it.
你会看到这个指令卸载了软件包又重新安装了一次 就像这样
Have fun with this exercise,
享受这个练习的乐趣
it really reinforces everything you've been practicing throughout this lesson.
它强化了你在这节课中实践的所有知识点